# Md. Ashiqur Rahman

Barisal Sadar, Barisal, Bangladesh

arshakib428@gmail.com Contact No: 01823359313

Linkedin: Ashiqur Rahman Shakib | LinkedIn

GitHub: https://github.com/arshakib

#### **SUMMARY**

Skilled and motivated web developer with extensive Learning in front-end and back-end development. Proficient in WordPress and MERN stack technologies. Demonstrated ability to lead teams and manage projects effectively with required soft skills like research, communication and teamwork, Public Speaking, Team Management, Leadership, problem-solving.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# Freelancers Club, Barisal

Developer (WordPress and MERN learning)
Barisal, Bangladesh
2022 - Present

- Developed and maintained WordPress websites for various clients, ensuring high-quality and responsive designs.
- Currently learning and implementing MERN stack technologies for dynamic web applications.
- Collaborated with the Barisal Government on multiple projects, ensuring compliance with government standards and regulations.

Soft Skills: Strong communication and teamwork (YouthNet, Barisal Blood Donors Club, NCTF)

# Dainik Vorer Angikar News Media, Barisal

Developer and IT Team Head (WordPress and MERN learning)
Barisal, Bangladesh
2022 - Present

- Led the IT team in developing and maintaining the news media website using WordPress.
- Implemented new features and functionalities to enhance user experience and engagement.
- Initiated the adoption of MERN stack technologies for future development projects, improving performance and scalability.

Soft Skills: Leadership, problem-solving (Hello.bdnews24.com, Youth Forum For Social Justice, Bangladesh Generation parliament)

# Life Event Management, Barisal

CO and IT Team Head (WordPress and MERN learning)
Barisal, Bangladesh
2022 - Present

- Led the IT team in developing and maintaining the social media, website.
- Implemented new features and functionalities to enhance user experience and engagement in social media and website.

Soft Skills: Public Speaking, Team Management (UNDP project, Come on Bangladesh, Life event management)

#### **EDUCATION**

## 1. SECONDARY SCHOOL CERTIFICATE

Institute : Collegiate Secondary School.

Group : science
Board : Barisal
Passing Year : 2021

Result : 4.78 in scale of 5.00.

# 2. CURRENT EDUCATION

Institute : Barishal polytechnic institutel

Department : Electrical Technology.

Board : Barisal Semester : 5th

#### **SKILLS**

- Proficient in WordPress development
- Learning in MERN stack technologies (MongoDB, Express.js, React.js, Node.js)
- HTML5, CSS, JavaScript

## PERSONAL INFORMATION

• Date of Birth: September 01, 2004

• Marital Status: Unmarried

· Religion: Islam

• Permanent Address: Vill: Bharipur, Post: Folagor, Thana: Bakergonj, District: Barishal

## **REFERENCE**

## **Sohanur Rahman**

Chief Executive, Protiki Jubo Sangshad (Bangladesh Model Youth Parliament

Coordinator) | YouthNet for Climate Justice

Mobile: +8801615917359 Email: kishanibd@gmail.com

Relation: Professional

#### Feroz Mostofa

Bureau Chief, Barisal

Mobile: +8801715917359

Email: fmostofa.reporter@gmail.com

Relation: Professional